A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1
  - England, 1/401
    - Admission Card to the laying of the foundation stone to the London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine, 1926 July 27; MISCELLANEOUS (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P-1H, L84c, no. 1 401
    - Elevation Drawing "The London School of Hygiene and Topical Medicine". Above the Elevation of Keepel Street. (P. Morley Horder and Verner O. Rees), ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P-1H, L84c, no. 2-10 401
    - Property Survey- "University of London Site Plan Proposal" Institute of Education, Law Institute and SOAS. (Denys Lasdun and Partners Chartered Architects), MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, L-4, N.W.3 401
    - Three Albany Terraces (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
    - Photocopy and Original Blueprint (2 Items) "The British Museum- Microfilm Laboratory". University Microfilms, Ann Arbor, Michigan, USA. Office of Wallace Frost (Eugene B. Power Esq), 1947 April 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, B2 4/28/47 (3)
    - The London School of Economics and East Side of Houghton Street, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, L84c, neg 401
    - Envelope containing 6 blueprints of the London School of Economics and East Side of Houghton Street, 1929 August 30; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 6) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, L84a, 1-6
    - Map of Houghton Street with envelope Property "Now in possession of School Owned by School Subject to Lease (7 Houghton Street) Not owned by School. From J.V. Licker, 1930 July 9; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, L84c, 401, LSE, P, L84c
    - Plot Plan "Oxford University, Suggested Extensions to Dyson Perrins Laboratory", ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, Ox2c
    - 2 copies of map on tissue paper "The London School of Economics and East Side of Houghton Street", MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      401, P, L84b
    - Blueprint negatives (4) "Bodleian Library Oxford - Board Street Building, received: 1936 April 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, Ox2b, 1
    - Plot Plan of the Ash Molean Museum in 4 formats., MISCELLANEOUS (Quantity 4); 4 formats available: Large Version on tissue paper, large blueprint negative, letter sized blueprint negative, and letter sized version on tissue paper. (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, Ox2, no.4
    - Sheldonian Theatre (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, Ox2, 3 neg
    - Map of Oxford, pasted on white paper, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      401, P, Ox2, no.1
    - Central Oxford, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      401, P, Ox2, no.2
    - "Bodleian Library", letter sized negative and colored pencil large scale on tissue paper., undated; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      401, P, Ox2, no.3
    - Hand-drawn map "Oxford University", 1931 Octobe 20; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      401, P, Ox2a
    - Proposed Additions to Strangeways Research Laboratory, Hills Road, Cambridge," Received with letter from W.E. Tisdale to Warren Weaver., 1937 October 13; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 1)
      P, Str-8,1
  - Australia, 1/410
    - Australia, Natural and Industrial Resources, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 3)
      M-P 410 Au-1
    - Australia with Travel Routes, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 3)
      M-P 410 Au-2
    - Radio Physics Division CSIRO 210ft. Dia Radio telescope, 1958 August 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 2)
      P, Com-1
    - Booklet of blueprints "University of Sydney Medical School, Rockefeller Foundation Building, WSC Fig, MK", BLUEPRINT (Drawer A 10, Folder 2)
      P-MS, Sy2, 1-8
    - "A Residence at Heron Island", University of Queensland, 1963 July; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 2)
      P, Q-1, 2
    - Biological Marine Research Station, Heron Island, University of Queensland, 1963 June; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 2)
      P, Q-1, 1
    - Blueprint of a Telescope Radio Physics Division CSIRO, Sydney Radio Telescope, General Arrangement, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 2)
      P, A-3
  - Fiji, 1/419
    - Layout of medical center, central medical school, and hospital., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 5) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8f, no. 1-5
    - Proposed laboratory and lecture room., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8, no. 3 & 4
    - "Type-No.5 Bungalow." Public Works Dept., Suva, BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, su8, no. 5
    - 5 architectural drawings: "Medical Dept., Fiji, Model NMP Station." Quarters and ground plans. H.S. Evans to G.K. Stroke., received: 1939 November 18; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 5) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-MS, Su8e, 1-5
    - Proposed Parasitology Laboratory, Gas House and Store Colonial War Memorial Hospital., 1935 November 20; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8c, 1 c. 1 & 2
    - Proposed Bacteriological Laboratory CWM Hospital Suva, Fiji., 1936 July 18; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8c, c. 1 & 2
    - Animal House on Roof of Parasitology Lab., 1936 August 18; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8c, 3
    - "Medical School, Suva, Student's Quarters." Ground and First Floor plans., 1927 July 16; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2). Oversized. (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8, no. 1 & 2
    - Booklet of 3 architectural drawings: Proposed Student Quarters Medical School, Received with letter VWT McGusty to GKS. Ground, 1st, and 2nd floor plan., 1940 April 20; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8, no. 6-8
    - Plan of Revised Interior Arrangement, Medical School., 1935 May 25; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8a
    - 2 copies of drawing: Diagrammatic Plan of Proposed Health Center and Outpatients Block, Received with letter SM Lambert to WA Sawyer., 1938 October 18; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2). Oversized. (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P-Ms, Su8d, 3 c. 1 & 2
    - Colonial War Memorial Hospital, Suva, Fiji. Sketch plan of proposed outpatient department and health center. Governor his Excellency, Sir Arthur Richards, KCMC. Received with letter, SM Lambert. Ground and 1st Floor, 1938 July 12; RENDERING (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P, Su8d, no. 1 & 2
    - War Memorial Hospital, Suva, Fiji." roposed Hostel for Non-European Nurses- Diagrammatic Plans. Received with letter VWT McGusty to GKS., 1940 April 20; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P, Su8b, no. 1, 2, & 3
    - 1 drawing: "War Memorial Hospital- Sketch Plan for Proposed Health Center and Outpatient Department." Received with letter VWT McGusty to GKS., 1940 April 20; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 3)
      P, Su8b, 4
  - Central America, 1/420
    - map of Central America "Ruins in the Maya Area (Guatemala, Honduras and Nicaragua)" (Department of Middle American Research-Tulane University), 1924, rev. 1929; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 3)
      M-P 420 C334
    - Mexico-Central America and West Indies, from (National Geographic Magazine), 1931 December; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 3)
      M-P 420 C37
    - Gulf of Mexico and Caribbean Sea (including the West Indies) "Localities in the Caribbean Region where Drainage Work for the Control of Malaria Has been Done in the Past or Is Still in Progress", 1940 August 28; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer A 1, Folder 4)
      M-P 420 C33I
  - Canada, 1/427
    - Province of Manitoba- Road & Highway System, 1942; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 3)
      M-P 427 M-1
    - Photocopies of 12 blueprints: "Hygiene and Public Health Building, University of Toronto." Floor plans and elevations., 1925 July; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 12) (Drawer A 10, Folder 4)
      P-1H, T63a, No. 1-12 Neg
    - New Brunswick Health Districts. Map 1- Health districts / Map 2- Medical Stations., 1925; MAP (Quantity 2). Oversized. (Drawer A 10, Folder 4)
      427 NB, M2
  - Bermuda, 1/430
    - 1 small drawing: "Bermuda Biological Station Proposed Staff Cottages, Sketch Plan And Elevations." RSM 1957 December 18 Memo., 1957 November 14; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 5)
      P, B-6, 430
  - Jamaica, 1/437
    - Map of Jamaica, 1888, rev. 1905 July; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M 437 J22c
    - Tuberculosis (Consumption) Poster, Jamaica. "Kills More Jamaicans than any other Disease.", POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 6)
      No # or Series Designations
    - 1 chart: "Belle Field School, 1st Vaccination.", 1938 February 8; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 6)
      437, T
    - Hospital for Tuberculosis, Number 145.", 1931 August 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2). Oversized. (Drawer A 10, Folder 6)
      P-H, Ja-I, No. 1 & 2
    - Chart II Control Group & Vaccinated Group., 1931; GRAPH (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 6)
      437, T2
    - X-Ray Laboratory and Surveys Dispensary with Letter of 1938 May 14. EW Hahiff to WA Sawyer Belle Field School (First Vaccination 1938 February 8), MISCELLANEOUS (Drawer A 10, Folder 6)
      437 T
    - Hospital for Tuberculosis, South, Sectional, North. (Drawer A 10, Folder 6)
      P-H, Ja-1, No. 2
  - Trinidad, 1/451
    - Colonial Microbiological Research Institute, Comiri. Pilot Plant, Outside Buildings and Floor Plan of Main Laboratory Block., ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 10, Folder 7)
      451 V
    - Colonial Microbiological Research Institute, Port of Spain, Trinidad., ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 10, Folder 7)
      P, Tr-1, 1
    - 2 drawings, 1 negative: "Maps, Trinidad Rainfall and Trinidad Ecological Zones." Received with letter of 1955 March 21,WG Downs to AJ Warren., MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 10, Folder 7)
      M, 1-2; 451, M, 3 (Negative)
  - Winward Islands, 1/455
    - Alterations to the Billharziasis Laboratory, Annex. St. Lucia., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 11); 2 small, 9 large (Drawer A 10, Folder 8)
      P, St.L.2, no. 1-11
  - Asia, 1/460
    - Map of Asia, 1942; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 460 As5
  - Ceylon, 1/462
    - City of Columbo (Ceylon/Sri Lanka), MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P462 C71
    - Map of Ceylon, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 462 C33d
    - Motor Map of Ceylon, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 462 C33b
    - Map of Ceylon, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 462 C33
  - India, 1/464
    - map of India, Pakistan, Burma and Ceylon, 1955; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 464 In-6 1955
    - India, Burma and Ceylon, 1955; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 464 In-1
    - India, Pakistan, Burma and Ceylon, 1955; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 464 In-2
    - Railways of India, 1933; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 464 In-3
    - Mysore and Coorg Province Map (provinces in India), 1934; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 464 My-1
    - India and Pakistan, 1932 August 23; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 464 In-7
    - Railway Map of India. Marked with RF Hookworm and Malaria work, 1935, 1936; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 2)
      M-P 464 In4
    - Part Plan of Lahore District Showing the Proposed Health Unit Area- Punjab" with letter from WPJ to WAS, 1940 May 7; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464J
    - "Ecological Studies" Pattukkottai, 1938-1939; GRAPH (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 Rus 2
    - Syllabus and academic calendar of Prince of Wales Medical College- Patna, 1926 July 1; MISCELLANEOUS (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464
    - Blueprints: "Movable Pen for Laying Hens- Virus Investigations." letter of 1953 February 26 JAK to WGD, BLUEPRINT (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
    - Mosquito Collection Stations- "Virus Research Centre- Department of Medical Entomology." North Aanara District, c. 1945; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
    - "Organizational chart "Virus Research Centre, Budget 1958-1959." Chart of Faculty and Staff hierarchy., GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
    - Proposed Internees & Residents Hostel, Gandhi Memorial Medical College, Lucknow." rec. with letter MEB to JCB, 1957 November 9; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P-MS L2
    - Ground Plan-Delhi University- Appendix III. University of Delhi- Faculty Development, 1964 December 15; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P De-1
    - Proposed Virus Research Centre, Poona., 1956 September 15; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P PO-1 4
    - Proposed Virus Research Centre, Poona., 1956 July-September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P PO-1 1, no. 1-3
    - booklet of plans and diagrams: "The Institute of Child Health- Calcutta." received with letter of 1958 May 7, Chare-JC Bugher., 1958 June 16; GRAPH (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 P C-1
    - 3 photocopies of blueprints: "American International School, New Delhi." Perspective, Ground, and 1st floor plan. Rec'd with letter of 1962 November 19 filed., 1961 December 10; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      PA15 1-3
    - :All India Institute of Medical Services- New Delhi, India" Received with letter of 1956 October 8, MCB-JCB, 1955 January 8; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      PA-1
    - 3 photocopies of blueprints: "Cold Storage for Cereal Laboratory - I.A.R.I.- Pusa, New Delhi." received with letter., 1959 July 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P IND- 3
    - Proposed Extension of the Library of the Indian Agricultural Research Institute- New Delhi., 1958 February 19; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 P Ind-1
    - Spiral-bound booklet: "Proposed Buildings for India International Centre." Contains drawings with architectural explanations and photos., 1960 May 25; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      PIIC-2
    - Proposed Site for Indian International Centre., ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 PIIC-1
    - Detailed Drawing Showing the Book Stack." Received with letter., 1960 March 5; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 P Ind-2
    - Proposed Monkey House and Rabbit House for the Virus Research Centre, Poona., 1952 March 10; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 P PO-2 3
    - 8 drawings: "Proposed Virus Research Centre, Poona." drawings of floor plans, diagrams, and notes., 1956 June 22; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 8) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 P PO-6 1-8
    - Site plan for Virus Research Centre, Poona., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
    - Rack for Mouse Boxes- Virus Research Centre, Poona., 1953 April 8; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P PO-5 1
    - Movable Pen for Laying Hens- Capacity., 1953 February 19; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P PO-3 1
    - Virus Research Laboratory- Poona, India, 1951 June 5; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 P PO-1 #1
    - Proposed Additions and Alterations in Pathological Dept. Bldgs. For Virus Research Centre at Poona- 1st fl., 1952 February 13; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P PO2 #2
    - B.J Medical College-Poona (India)- Old Pathology Building. Layout, Elevation, and ground plan., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P-MS PO-1 #1, 2, 3
    - 1 small drawing and 1 blueprint: "Bombay Municipal Corporation- Proposed Additional Floors over the Existing Registration & O.P.D Blocks in the K.E.M. Hospital for the Depts. Of Medicine & Surgery", BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P-MS SE-1 #1 & 2
    - "Christian Medical Hospital- Proposed Out-patient Department." Ground, 1st floor, and elevation plans., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 P-MS V-2 3/P-MS V-1 5
    - "Christian Medical Hospital-Old Out-patient Building- Plan of 1st Floor.", ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      P-MS V-1 1 & 2
    - 1 organizational chart: "Virus Research Centre- Budget- Depts. Of Virology, Field Epidemiology, Medical Zoology and Medical Entomology.", 1957-1958; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 C-1
    - Map of Neyyattinkara Health Unit- Travancore, India., received: 1937 February 19; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 M72
    - Health Training Centre- Closepet., received: 1937 February 19; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 M73
    - Health Unit- Poonamallee., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 M74
    - "The Sawantwari State- Spleen Indices in the Year 1928"., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 M29
    - Kolgaon, MAP (Quantity 22) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 M41-52; 464 M 58-67
    - 10 Maps & photographs- enclosed with 1952 Annual Report for East Region by RB Watson, MAP (Quantity 10) (Drawer A 11, Folder 1)
      464 M-1 (a-j)
  - Pakistan, 1/465
    - Map of Pakistan, 1951; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 1)
      M-P 465 Pa-1
  - Papua, 1/472
    - Resource of the Territory of Papua New Guinea, Vol. 2 maps, 1951; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
      M-P 472 PA-1
  - Malaysia, 1/473
    - map of Burma, Malaya and Indochina, 1951; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 2)
  - Africa, 1/475
    - Uganda, 1943 May; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 1)
      M-P 475 Ug 2
    - Lake Victoria-Belgian Congo- Kalangala., 1943 September; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 1)
      M-3 475 Ug 1
    - West Africa: "West African Yellow Fever Commission- yellow fever cases", 1927; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M35a
    - Royal Khassa Mostrod." Egypt. Received with letter CH Barlow, 1936 February 2; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M 8
    - Colonies of Africa in which Protection Tests have been Carried Out to Determine the Distribution and Limits of Yellow Fever.", MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M 106
    - 1 photocopy of map: "Reported cases of Yellow Fever in Downtown Accra, Gold Coast.", MAP (Quantity 1); letter-size (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M37
    - Yellow Fever Reports in West Africa by Country., 1931; MAP (Quantity 6) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M83
    - Yellow Fever Service: Dry Bulb Temperatures and Relative Humidities in Different Parts of Nigeria. Received with letter no. 1448, 6/22/1931 from A.F. Mahaffi to FFR, 1931 June 22; MAP (Quantity 7) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M72-M78
    - Cities and Towns of West Africa where Yellow Fever has been Reported, with Years in which Disease Occurred.", 1924 December; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M9b
    - Yellow Fever Service, based on previous entry "Cities and Towns of West Africa where Yellow Fever has been Reported, with Years in which Disease Occurred.", 1924; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M70, M71
    - Series of 7 photostat copies of map of "Bwamba" copies for Yellow Fever Service (illustrations by Mahaffy and Haddow), MAP (Quantity 7) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      477 M Bb-1-6
    - West Africa, showing yellow fever cases reported in 1925 (1 original and 3 copies), MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M20a
    - 1 chart "Serum Immunity Tests in the Lagos Laboratory", GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M71 Pr II
    - 4 Maps (3 on mylar) "Yellow Fever Protection Tests: Location of Ibadan and surrounding towns where protection tests were carried out", MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
    - Map of West Africa "Cities and Towns of West Africa where Yellow Fever has been reported in 1927", MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M33
    - West Africa "Yellow Fever Commission" Various Maps of Yellow Fever Investigations and reported cases, 1926; MAP (Quantity 5) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M30, M31, M32, M21
    - West Africa "Yellow Fever reported in 1925, 1926 and 1925 and 1926" Map shows cases for each individual year described, MAP (Quantity 1); letter-sized. (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M21
    - 3 charts of Egypt and Algeria "Algeria: Officially reported cases Typhus fever" "Egypt Monthly Incidence of Typhus Fever 1926-1935" "Monthly Incidence of Typhus Fever 1926-1935: Morocco, Algeria, Tunisia", GRAPH (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      474 G1, G2, G3
    - Gold Coast and Nigeria "Yellow Fever Work- Monkey and Mouse Protection Tests", MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 11, Folder 2)
      475 M79, M80
  - Kenya, 1/476
    - Provisional Malaria map of East Africa- Abyssinia, 1943; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 4)
      476 I M Ea 1
    - Provisional Malaria map of East Africa- Kenya Colony, 1943; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 4)
      476 I M Ea 2
    - Provisional Malaria map of East Africa- Kenya Colony, 1943; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 4)
      476 I M Ea 3
    - Provisional Malaria map of East Africa- Kenya Colony, 1943; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 4)
      476 I M Ea 4
    - 1 Topographic map "Location Map of Njoro Area" received with letter, 1952 December 13; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 11, Folder 3)
      P Eg-1
    - Royal College Chiromo Veterinary Pre-Clinical School Preliminary Sketch Plans, 1962 May 28; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer A 11, Folder 3)
      P R-VM 1, 2 and 3
    - 2 Site maps "Egerton Agricultural College, Njoro" development plan and sketch of dining hall, 1962 March 18; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer A 11, Folder 3)
      P Eg 2 and 3
  - Mauritius, 1/478
    - Mauritius, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 1)
      M-3 478 M44b
  - North Africa, 1/485
    - Northern Lebanon and Syria, 1948; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 1, Folder 1)
      M-P 485
  - South Africa region, 1/487
    - commercial maps from South Africa, 1960s-1990; MAP (Quantity 5) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 1)
      Includes the following maps: "Salisbury & Bulawayo" (Mobil); "Federation of Rhodesia & Nyasaland" (gov't map from Rhodesia); "Shell Road Map of Botswana" (Shell); "Road Map of Southern Africa" (Caltex); "'Central & South Africa and Madagascar" (Michelin).
    - commercial maps of the Republic of Botswana, 1985; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 2)
      Includes the following maps: "Chobe" and "Okavango Delta" (scale 1: 350,000) (published by Department of Surveys & Lands, Gaborone).
    - Republic of Botswana: Elevations (scale 1:1,500,000) (published by Department of Surveys & Lands, Gaborone), 1986; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 2)
    - Malawi (scale 1:100,000) (published by Department of Surveys, Vlantyre), 1985; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 2)
    - "Routes of the Early European Travelers in Federation of Rhodesia and Nyasaland" (scale 1:20,000) (text on back gives lists of European travelers on expeditions) (published by Federal Government Printer of Rhodesia & Nyasaland), 1964; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 2)
    - road map of Namibia (scale 1:3,450,000) (published by Caltex), 1983; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 2)
    - road map of Southwest Africa (scale 1:2,500,000) (published by Dept. of Transport of Southwest Africa), 1988; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 2)
    - sheets 1-4 of set of road maps of Zimbabwe with elevations, etc. (scale 1:500,000) (Department of the Surveyor General of Rhodesia), 1978; MAP (Quantity 5) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 2)